<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>The personal page of Jeremie Clos on Jeremie Clos</title>
    <link>https://jclos.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content in The personal page of Jeremie Clos on Jeremie Clos</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://jclos.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://jclos.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jclos.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>About Me I did my PhD in the Robert Gordon University, with a SICSA Prize studentship to research argumentation stance mining in social media. I have been lucky to hold many different roles, from software engineering and data science positions in a tech startup in Edinburgh to several research and teaching contracts in the University of Toulouse, the Robert Gordon University, and the University of Nottingham. I have worked in many teams and with a multitude of people of different backgrounds: software engineers, computer scientists, petroleum geologists, education researchers, and many I am forgetting, which has given me a taste for interdisciplinary research.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Allocations</title>
      <link>https://jclos.github.io/posts/2023-spring-allocation-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jclos.github.io/posts/2023-spring-allocation-01/</guid>
      <description>Keep in mind that this is a live table that can be changed as the term progresses and circumstances change.
Spring 2023 Edit 1 on 25/01/2023 @ 00:44
Last changed on 01/02/2023 @ 18:27
Modules    Module Teaching support team     COMP1003 (FSE) Yong Kok ; Sammie Fuller ; Damla Kilic   COMP1004 (DBI) Kavan Fatehi ; Vivek Thaminni Ramamoorthy ; Ifeoma Ogbodo ; Nazia Hameed ; Chao Chen ; Susan Ali   COMP1008 (FAI) Kavan Fatehi ; Hoang Le ; Salim Maaji ; Victoria Hann ; Rebecca Tickle ; Weiyao Meng ; Warren Jackson   COMP1009 (Java) (PGPJ) Hoang Le ; Nazia Hameed ; Kristian Spoerer ; Susan Ali ; Damla Kilic ; Rebecca Tickle ; Warren Jackson ; Liz Felton   COMP1009 (Haskell) (PGPH) Joshua Chen ; Stefania Damato ; Jacob Neumann ; Brandon Hewer ; Colm Baston ; Johannes Schipp von Branitz ; Stiephen Pradal ; Ian Knight   COMP1043 (MCS2) Dimah Almani ; Johannes Schipp von Branitz ; Liz Felton   COMP2001/COMP2011 (AIM) Kavan Fatehi ; Hoang Le ; Salman Arif ; Krishika Khemani ; Warren Jackson   COMP2003 (AFP) Ian Knight   COMP2004 (HCI) Susan Ali ; Damla Kilic   COMP2005 (IIP) Ziling Wu ; Victoria Hann ; Kristian Spoerer   COMP2006 (CPP) Han Meng ; Salman Arif ; Ifeoma Ogbodo ; Chao Chen ; Liz Felton   COMP2009 (ACE) Salim Maaji ; Alexander Dewfall ; Salman Arif ; Kristian Spoerer ; Ian Knight ; Warren Jackson   COMP2010 (SOF) Nazia Hameed ; Adam Walker   COMP2012 (LAC) Salman Arif ; Jacob Neumann ; Ian Knight   COMP3004/COMP4105 (DIA) Adam Walker   COMP3006 (SEC) Salwa Alotaibi ; Samiah Alghamdi   COMP3007/COMP4106 (CV) Zhendi Gong ; Zeyang Liu   COMP3011 (GRA) Kavan Fatehi ; Lewis Stuart ; Kristian Spoerer   COMP3021/COMP 3022 (VIS) Jimiama Mafeni Mase ; Phuong Nguyen ; Susan Ali ; Damla Kilic   COMP3077 (CRY) Alexander Dewfall   COMP4002 (GAM) Dimah Almani ; Luke Skarth-Hayley   COMP4024 (SPM) Susan Ali   COMP4030 (DSML) Han Meng ; Johann Benerradi ; Nazia Hameed ; Weiyao Meng   COMP4033 (FUZ) Te Zhang ; Yu Zhao   COMP4036 (MRT) Jude Afana ; Harriet Cameron ; Christine Li ; Callum Berger ; Joshua Duvnjak ; Damla Kilic   COMP4037 (REM) Michael Harmson ; Vivek Thaminni Ramamoorthy ; Susan Ali ; Damla Kilic   COMP4038 (SOD) Adam Walker ; Weiyao Meng   COMP4103 (BIG) Kavan Fatehi ; Salman Arif ; Jimiama Mafeni Mase ; Rebecca Tickle   COMP4101 (MAL) Ian Knight    PGR Students    Name Module(s)     Yong Kok COMP1003 (FSE)   Kavan Fatehi COMP1004 (DBI) ; COMP1008 (FAI) ; COMP2001/COMP2011 (AIM) ; COMP3011 (GRA) ; COMP4103 (BIG)   Hoang Le COMP1008 (FAI) ; COMP1009 (Java) (PGPJ) ; COMP2001/COMP2011 (AIM)   Han Meng COMP2006 (CPP) ; COMP4030 (DSML)   Zhendi Gong COMP3007/COMP4106 (CV)   Te Zhang COMP4033 (FUZ)   Jude Afana COMP4036 (MRT)   Salim Maaji COMP1008 (FAI) ; COMP2009 (ACE)   Zeyang Liu COMP3007/COMP4106 (CV)   Dimah Almani COMP1043 (MCS2) ; COMP4002 (GAM)   Johann Benerradi COMP4030 (DSML)   Alexander Dewfall COMP2009 (ACE) ; COMP3077 (CRY)   Salman Arif COMP2001/COMP2011 (AIM) ; COMP2006 (CPP) ; COMP2009 (ACE) ; COMP2012 (LAC) ; COMP4103 (BIG)   Joshua Chen COMP1009 (Haskell) (PGPH)   Stefania Damato COMP1009 (Haskell) (PGPH)   Yu Zhao COMP4033 (FUZ)   Lewis Stuart COMP3011 (GRA)   Jacob Neumann COMP1009 (Haskell) (PGPH) ; COMP2012 (LAC)   Luke Skarth-Hayley COMP4002 (GAM)   Krishika Khemani COMP2001/COMP2011 (AIM)   Ziling Wu COMP2005 (IIP)   Jimiama Mafeni Mase COMP3021/COMP 3022 (VIS) ; COMP4103 (BIG)   Brandon Hewer COMP1009 (Haskell) (PGPH)   Harriet Cameron COMP4036 (MRT)   Christine Li COMP4036 (MRT)   Colm Baston COMP1009 (Haskell) (PGPH)   Callum Berger COMP4036 (MRT)   Joshua Duvnjak COMP4036 (MRT)   Johannes Schipp von Branitz COMP1009 (Haskell) (PGPH) ; COMP1043 (MCS2)   Stiephen Pradal COMP1009 (Haskell) (PGPH)   Salwa Alotaibi COMP3006 (SEC)   Samiah Alghamdi COMP3006 (SEC)   Victoria Hann COMP1008 (FAI) ; COMP2005 (IIP)   Phuong Nguyen COMP3021/COMP 3022 (VIS)   Michael Harmson COMP4037 (REM)   Vivek Thaminni Ramamoorthy COMP1004 (DBI) ; COMP4037 (REM)   Sammie Fuller COMP1003 (FSE)   Ifeoma Ogbodo COMP1004 (DBI) ; COMP2006 (CPP)    Teaching Associates    Name Modules     Nazia Hameed COMP1004 (DBI) ; COMP1009 (Java) (PGPJ) ; COMP2010 (SOF) ; COMP4030 (DSML)   Chao Chen COMP1004 (DBI) ; COMP2006 (CPP)   Kristian Spoerer COMP1009 (Java) (PGPJ) ; COMP2005 (IIP) ; COMP2009 (ACE) ; COMP3011 (GRA)   Ian Knight COMP1009 (Haskell) (PGPH) ; COMP2003 (AFP) ; COMP2009 (ACE) ; COMP2012 (LAC) ; COMP4101 (MAL)   Susan Ali COMP1004 (DBI) ; COMP1009 (Java) (PGPJ) ; COMP2004 (HCI) ; COMP3021/COMP 3022 (VIS) ; COMP4024 (SPM) ; COMP4037 (REM)   Adam Walker COMP2010 (SOF) ; COMP3004/COMP4105 (DIA) ; COMP4038 (SOD)   Damla Kilic COMP1003 (FSE) ; COMP1009 (Java) (PGPJ) ; COMP2004 (HCI) ; COMP3021/COMP 3022 (VIS) ; COMP4036 (MRT) ; COMP4037 (REM)   Rebecca Tickle COMP1008 (FAI) ; COMP1009 (Java) (PGPJ) ; COMP4103 (BIG)   Weiyao Meng COMP1008 (FAI) ; COMP4030 (DSML) ; COMP4038 (SOD)   Warren Jackson COMP1008 (FAI) ; COMP1009 (Java) (PGPJ) ; COMP2001/COMP2011 (AIM) ; COMP2009 (ACE)   Liz Felton COMP1009 (Java) (PGPJ) ; COMP1043 (MCS2) ; COMP2006 (CPP)    </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Computer Graphics</title>
      <link>https://jclos.github.io/cg/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jclos.github.io/cg/</guid>
      <description>Computer Graphics Back to modules
Teaching team  Jeremie Clos Vaughan Wang Kristian Spoerer  Core ideas of the module Understanding 3D geometry and 3D transformations, how they relate to what appears on your screen, and how to go from intuition to mathematical formulation to implementation.
Recommended reading Other reading </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://jclos.github.io/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jclos.github.io/contact/</guid>
      <description>E-mail  Personal: name.surname@gmail.com Professional: name.surname@nottingham.ac.uk  If you are a student, I would encourage you to read this small guide to e-mail communication before contacting me. It can change based on circumstances, but my general policy is the following:
 I do not e-mail or read e-mails during the week-end. I do not e-mail or read e-mails before 9 AM and after 6 PM. I typically check my e-mails at regular, pre-planned intervals.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Data Science and Machine Learning</title>
      <link>https://jclos.github.io/dsml/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jclos.github.io/dsml/</guid>
      <description>COMP4030: Data Science and Machine Learning Back to modules
Teaching team  Praminda Caleb-Solly Jeremie Clos  Core ideas of the module An opinionated introduction to the core challenges of data science and machine learning.
This module will enable you to appreciate the range of data analysis problems that can be modelled computationally and a range of techniques that are suitable to analyse and solve those problems. Topics covered include: basic statistics; types of data; data visualisation techniques; data modelling; data pre-processing methods including data imputation; forecasting methods; clustering and classification methods (decision trees, naīve bayes classifiers, k-nearest neighbours); data simulation and model interpretation techniques to aid decision support.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Databases, Interfaces and Software design</title>
      <link>https://jclos.github.io/dis/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jclos.github.io/dis/</guid>
      <description>Databases, Interfaces (and Software design) Back to modules
Teaching team  Stuart Reeves Jeremie Clos  Core ideas of the module Understanding the architecture of web applications from data storage to presentation to the users.
In this module we focus on the structure of databases, including how to make them fast, efficient and reliable and on the ways of interacting with them via user interfaces. We examine the fundamentals of the relational database model, its mathematical basis, as well as implementations of the model in database management systems (DBMS) and languages to interact with them such as Structured Query Language (SQL).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Human-AI Interaction</title>
      <link>https://jclos.github.io/hii/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jclos.github.io/hii/</guid>
      <description>COMP3074: Human-AI Interaction Back to modules
Teaching team  Joel Fischer Jeremie Clos  Core ideas of the module Understanding the challenges of human-AI interaction from a sociological and technical perspective.
This module is part of the Human-Computer Interaction theme, and the Artificial Intelligence and Optimisation theme in the School of Computer Science. It is an introduction to the design of human-AI interaction to ensure the AI-driven systems we built are beneficial and useful to people.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sending e-mails and basic academic politeness</title>
      <link>https://jclos.github.io/posts/emails-and-politeness/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jclos.github.io/posts/emails-and-politeness/</guid>
      <description>Sending e-mails and basic academic politeness Jeff Leek had an excellent blog post from 2011 on getting e-mails responses from busy people, which seems to have disappeared recently. While his recommendations are quite strict, they are a good idea of general guidelines university students should pick up when trying to communicate with most academics, who are almost always busy people. Here is my expanded version of those rules:
 RULE 1.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Teaching</title>
      <link>https://jclos.github.io/teaching/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jclos.github.io/teaching/</guid>
      <description>Modules    Academic Year Term Module     2022-2023 Spring Data Science and Machine Learning   2022-2023 Autumn Human-AI Interaction   2021-2022 Spring Computer Graphics ; Data Modelling and Analysis   2021-2022 Autumn Human-AI Interaction ; Databases, Interfaces and Software design   2020-2021 Spring Computer Graphics   2020-2021 Autumn Human-AI Interaction ; Databases, Interfaces and Software design   2019-2020 Spring Databases and Interfaces ; Computer Graphics   2019-2020 Autumn Databases, Interfaces and Software design    Data Science and Machine Learning (Formerly Data Modelling and Analysis)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Teaching and Projects</title>
      <link>https://jclos.github.io/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jclos.github.io/projects/</guid>
      <description>Projects In this page I centralise all there is to know about my projects. If you want to know how to write your own project proposal so that it is not completely terrible, click here. If you are looking for the list of projects I am interested in supervising, click here.
Undergraduate and Postgraduate Projects CLICK HERE TO JUMP TO PROJECTS
1. Read this first If you contact me and it is obvious from your e-mail that you did not read this page, I will ignore your request.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
