<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Jeremie Clos</title>
    <link>https://jclos.github.io/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Jeremie Clos</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://jclos.github.io/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>A reading list for the starting grad student</title>
      <link>https://jclos.github.io/posts/a-reading-list/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jclos.github.io/posts/a-reading-list/</guid>
      <description>Go back to ramblings
A reading list for the grad student (who doesn&amp;rsquo;t know what to read) One thing I deeply regret about starting my graduate studies is the progressive loss of taste for casual reading. You feel trapped between wanting to read and the guilt of the reading material not being related to your work and end up associating the two, leading to simply not reading at all. Here is an attempt at a reading list of books about academia which I found useful, entertaining or something in between, while not being directly related to one&amp;rsquo;s research topic:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fighting stillness: lifting weights for the busy academic</title>
      <link>https://jclos.github.io/posts/lifting-weights/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jclos.github.io/posts/lifting-weights/</guid>
      <description>Go back to ramblings
Fighting stillness: lifting weights for the busy academic Anybody who has met me knows that my main form of activity consists in the very simple sport of lifting weights (and putting them back down). There is an elegance in the simplicity of strength training that attracts me, and I have spent a long time trying to find a way to work that into my busy life as a graduate student and early career academic.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sending e-mails and basic academic politeness</title>
      <link>https://jclos.github.io/posts/emails-and-politeness/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jclos.github.io/posts/emails-and-politeness/</guid>
      <description>Go back to ramblings
Sending e-mails and basic academic politeness Jeff Leek has an excellent blog post from 2011 on getting e-mails responses from busy people. While his recommendations are quite strict, they are a good idea of general guidelines university students should pick up when trying to communicate with most academics, who are almost always busy people. His rules are the following:
 RULE 1. Limit the number of e-mails you send to that person to one a day.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The unreasonable effectiveness of writing badly</title>
      <link>https://jclos.github.io/posts/writing-badly/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jclos.github.io/posts/writing-badly/</guid>
      <description>Go back to ramblings
Writing often and badly One of the few things I have learned about myself when trying to write is that perfectionism can kill any sort of motivation one might have. But how does it do so? In my case, it does it by making me stop and thinking about the perfect sentences to put on paper. I got out of this vicious circle by applying two pieces of advice coming from two authors that could not be more different from each other:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You can only slice a pie so many times</title>
      <link>https://jclos.github.io/posts/slicing-pies/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jclos.github.io/posts/slicing-pies/</guid>
      <description>Go back to ramblings
You can only slice a pie so many times before you are left with crumbs TBD</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
